buzzbuzzhome.com 2019-05-07

# None

At BuzzBuzzHome (“we” or “us” or “our”), we value and respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. This privacy policy demonstrates our firm commitment to your privacy. We appreciate your use of our website and encourage you to read this privacy policy to understand how we collect, use and process your information. 

We collect information that you share with us when using BuzzBuzzHome.

When you sign up for a BuzzBuzzHome account, certain information is required such as your full name and email address. You may also choose to provide information such as your location, a personal website, a personal bio, or an image. Your name, image, personal bio, personal website and location may be publicly displayed. BuzzBuzzHome does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. BuzzBuzzHome retains this information only as long as the profile is active.

When you partake in a paid service program (such as the Feature program or BuzzPro), we may collect your financial information to process payments. This information will be used only to complete payments and will not be shared. All financial information is encrypted and stored securely.

When you communicate with BuzzBuzzHome or use BuzzBuzzHome to communicate with other BuzzBuzzHome users, we collect information about your communication and any information you provide. When you fill a form or post to forums, we collect any information you choose to provide.

If you link, connect or login to BuzzBuzzHome through a third party service (e.g. Facebook), the third party service may send us information such as your profile information. This information may vary and is controlled by that service.

We collect information automatically when using BuzzBuzzHome.

When using BuzzBuzzHome, we collect information about the pages or other content you view, the forms you’ve submitted, the edits you make and other actions on the BuzzBuzzHome website. We collect information about your interactions with the site (eg. mouse movements, locations, clicks and key presses) for the purpose of improving user experience.

When using BuzzBuzzHome, we collect your general location through your IP address to serve you relevant information. We may request your specific information to improve your search experience.

When using BuzzBuzzHome, we collect log information such as IP address, preferred language, access times, hardware/software information and device information to help diagnose problems on our server and to administer our website. This information is also used to gather broad, aggregated demographic information.

BuzzBuzzHome and Third Party Partners use cookies and other similar technologies, such as pixels. These cookies are used for targeted advertising on and off the BuzzBuzzHome site, to deliver specific content for your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to estimate our audience size through demographic information, to monitor and analyze the performance, operation and effectiveness of our site.

BuzzBuzzHome contains links to third party sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party websites. BuzzBuzzHome's co-branded sites and content partner sites may have privacy policies independent of BuzzBuzzHome. This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on pages hosted on BuzzBuzzHome. BuzzBuzzHome may share aggregate information with trading partners, co-branded sites, and advertisers. However, this aggregated information does not contain personally identifiable information.

BuzzBuzzHome has security measures in place to help protect your information against loss, access, alteration, misuse and interception by third parties. BuzzBuzzHome cannot guarantee and assumes no liability for the security of transmission or storage of your information. 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email or other forms of communications from BuzzBuzzHome. To opt-out of receiving emails, click on the notifications tab while editing your user profile to change your settings.

If you do not wish to be tracked via cookies, you may disable the usage of cookies through your browser settings.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with BuzzBuzzHome, you can contact: [privacy@buzzbuzzhome.com](mailto:privacy@buzzbuzzhome.com)

Last Revised: September 19, 2017
